Soviet Union and Russia Orthodox Subject Files, Inclusive: 1922 — 2018, undated, Bulk: 1970-1992
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- General, 1922-2018, undated; 1
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and Science, 1976-1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Secular Education, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Philosophy, 1954, 1972-1991 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Morality and Ethics, 1973-1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theological Education (1 of7), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theological Education (2 of 7), 1957-1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theological Education (3 of 7), 1976-1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theological Education (4 of 7), 1981-1990, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theological Education (5 of 7), 1991-2006 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theological Education (6 of 7), undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theological Education (7 of 7), 1988, 1993-2006 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religious Education of Children, 1970, 1972, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and Intelligentsia, 1977-1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Unity. Schisms. Cults, 1980, 1994, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Philosophy of Unity, 1978, 1993, 1994, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Heresy and Cults, 1977-1980, 1992-1993, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Karlovatsky Schism (1 of 3), 1934, 1936, 1967-2006, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Karlovatsky Schism (2 of 3), 1934, 1936, 1967-2006, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Karlovatsky Schism (3 of 3), 1934, 1936, 1967-2006, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Statistics (1 of 2), 1955-2007, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Statistics (2 of 2), 1955-2007, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. General (1 of 2), 1972-2000, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. General (2 of 2), 1972-2000, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Ecumenical Relations with Individuals, 1980, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. American Autocephaly, 1968-1990, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Ukrainian Autocephaly, 1961, 1969-1998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Ukrainian Autocephaly. Articles by Bohdan Bociurkiw, 1960-1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Japanese Autonomy, 1970-1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Constantinople, 1966-1979, 1987, 1988, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical relations with Fellow Believers. Mount Athos, 1967-1986, 1991- 1992, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Pan-Orthodox, 1971-1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Christian Ecumenism, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Russian Orthodox Church Abroad, 1956, 1974-1989 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Fellow Believers. Russian Orthodox Church Abroad, 1990-2007 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations, 1962-1998, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations. General Interdenominational (1 of 3), 1950-1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations. General Interdenominational (2 of 3), 1971-1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations. General Interdenominational (3 of 3), 1971, 1973, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. A-I, 1976-2002 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. J-U, 1971-1999, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. Anglican Church (1 of 2), 1943, 1962-1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. Anglican Church (2 of 2), 1977-2001, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. North America, 1963-1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. Old Believers, 1971-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. Old Catholics, 1967-1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. Roman Catholic Church (1 of 2), 1968-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Ecumenical Relations with Specific Denominations. Roman Catholic Church (2 of 2), 1986-2002 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations Outside the USSR, 1977-1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations Outside the USSR. Conference of European Churches, 1961-1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations Outside the USSR. World Council of Churches (1 of 4), 1962-1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations Outside the USSR. World Council of Churches (2 of 4), 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations Outside the USSR. World Council of Churches (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations Outside the USSR. World Council of Churches (4 of 4), 1977-2006, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Ecumenical Contacts with Other Denominations Outside the USSR. Vatican, 1962-1990, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Outside Russia. Russian Ecclesiastical Mission in Jerusalem, 1923-1972 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Outside Russia. Russian Ecclesiastical Mission in Jerusalem, 1965-1991, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity, 1972-2000, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. All-Russian Social Christians (1 of 2), 1968-1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. All-Russian Social Christians (2 of 2), 1976-1987, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. Russian Patriots, 1971-1987, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. Neo-Slavophilism, 1973-1985, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. Language, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. Nationalist Publications. Veche (1 of 2), 1970-1974 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. Nationalist Publications. Veche (2 of 2), 1975-1981, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and National Identity. Nationalist Publications. Zemlia, 1974-1981, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Involvement in Secular Affairs, 1979-1999 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs (1 of 2), 1965-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs (2 of 2), 1980-2001, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs. Mediation in the 1993 Crisis., 1993, September-October (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Contacts with Secular Organizations and Conferences, 1976-1988 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Christian Political Bodies, 1979-1999 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Involvement in Military Affairs, 1991-2002 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Peace Activities. General (1 of 2), 1964, 1975-1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Peace Activities. General (2 of 2), 1981-1999, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Peace Activities. Christian Peace Conference, 1969-1980, 1988, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Art. Architecture. Music. Literature. General, 1965-1977, 1988, 1991, 1997, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Art. Architecture., 1980, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Individual Artists, 1974-1979, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Music, 1974-2007, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Music. Korolev, Igor, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Music. Jordanville, USA, 2005-2006 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Art. General, 1966-1989, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Art. Icons (1 of 2), 1963, 1971-1982, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Art. Icons (2 of 2), 1983-2005, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Architecture. Restoration (1 of 6), 1965 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Architecture. Restoration (2 of 6), 1903, 1924, 1959-1968 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Architecture. Restoration (3 of 6), 1969-1975 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Architecture. Restoration (4 of 6), 1976-1979 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Architecture. Restoration (5 of 6), 1980-1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Architecture. Restoration (6 of 6), 1990-2006, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature, 1914, 1972-1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Bible, 1975-1991, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Women, 1975-1981, 1991, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Children and Youth (1 of 2), 1964-1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Children and Youth (2 of 2), 1972-2000, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Sociology. Family, 1970-2001 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Corruption in the Russian Orthodox Church, 1995-1999, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Visual Materials. General, 1967-2003, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Visual Material. Bible Illustration, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Visual Materials. Postcards Sets, 1971, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Visual Materials. Images of Churches, Icons, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Visual Materials. Moscow Theological Academy, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Visual Materials. Individuals, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Visual Materials. Individual Clergy, 1974-1975, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Social Concept of the Moscow Patriarchate, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Individual Clergy. Kuraev, Andrei, Deacon, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Articles about Fr. Alexander Men', 1990-1998, 2013, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Fr. Alexander Men's Open Orthodox University, 1993-1997 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Fr. Alexander Men' Radio Program. Men's Ministries, 1994, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Clippings from German Press, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Clippings from German Press, 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Rebuilding, Restoration and Reopening of Orthodox Churches, 1987-1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Campaign to Rebuild and Restore Churches, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Rebuilding, Restoration and Reopening of Orthodox Churches. Cathedral of Christ the Savior, 1990-1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Rebuilding, Restoration and Reopening of Orthodox Churches. Cathedral of the Icon of the Kazan Mother of God in the Red Square, 1990-1993 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Return of Church Property, 1989-1996 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Building of Churches, 1985,1990 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Vandalism and Theft, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Samizdat, 1914-2008, undated; 2
  Samizdat Orthodox Subject Files contain materials pertaining to the persecution of Russian Orthodox believers fighting for their freedom of religion. The materials include unofficially circulated documents, reports, appeals, addresses, original and translated literary works, and other materials which never passed through Soviet censorship and were not officially published. This series is in good condition.
  - History of the Russian Orthodox Church. General, 1977, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - History of the Russian Orthodox Church. Soviet Period, 1982-1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers, 1977, 1981-1987 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Agursky, Mikhail, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Barabanov, Evgenii, 1972, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Bombin, Mikhail, 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Brennikov (Serebrennikov), Nikolai, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Delone, Vadim, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Gorbanevskaia, Nataliia, 1969-1970 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Grigor'ev, Viktor, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ivanov, Iurii, 1974, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Karelin, Feliks, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Khodorovich, Sergei, 1983, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Krakhmal'nikova Zoia, 1979-1988, 1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Levitin (Krasnov), Anatolii, 1970, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Levitin (Krasnov), Anatolii, 1974 March (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Markus, Sergei, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Martynov, Ivan, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ogorodnikov Aleksandr (1 of 5), 1976-1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ogorodnikov Aleksandr (2 of 5), 1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ogorodnikov Aleksandr (3 of 5), 1986 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ogorodnikov Aleksandr (4 of 5), 1987-1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ogorodnikov Aleksandr (5 of 5), 1978-1987 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ogurtsov, Igor (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ogurtsov, Igor (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Osipov, Vladimir, 1983-1987 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Pashnin, Evgenii, 1979, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Petrov-Agatov, Aleksandr, 1968, 1976, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Protsenko, Pavel, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Ratushinskaia, Irina, 1982-1987 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Regel'son, Lev, 1977, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Senderov, Valerii (1 of 2), 1982-1987 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Senderov, Valerii (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii, 1972-1978, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (1 of 10), 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (2 of 10), 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (3 of 10), 1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (4 of 10), 1975 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (5 of 10), 1975 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (6 of 10), 1975 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (7 of 10), 1976 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (8 of 10), 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (9 of 10), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Shimanov, Gennadii. Manuscripts (10 of 10), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Svetov, Feliks, 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Talantov, Boris, 1967-1969 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers. Zotov, Mikhail, 1986, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Administration, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. List of Churches, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Individual Churches, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Patriarchate (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Patriarchate (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. 1961 Council of Bishops (1 of 2), 1961, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. 1962 Council of Bishops (2 of 2), 1961, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. 1971 Local Council of Bishops (1 of 3), 1971, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. 1972 Local Council of Bishops (2 of 3), 1971, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. 1973 Local Council of Bishops (3 of 3), 1971, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Dioceses, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church-State Relations, 1964, 1975-1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church-State Relations. Individual Cases, 1975-1979 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Opening and Consecration of Russian Orthodox Churches and Chapels, 1987, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Opening New Russian Orthodox Church in Naberezhnye Chelny, 1980-1983 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Opening New Russian Orthodox Church in Kotovo, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Opening New Russian Orthodox Church in Lozovaia, Kharkov Oblast', 1979 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Oppressive Practices towards the Russian Orthodox Church, 1964, 1971-1977, 1980-1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Interrogations of Orthodox Believers, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers, 1979-1984 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers. Khodorovich, Sergei, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers. Kukobaka, Mikhail, 1979, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers. Lapkin, Ivan, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers. Oros Family, 1982, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers. Poresh, Vladimir, 1980, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers. Protsenko, Pavel, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Trials of Orthodox Believers. Velikanova, Tat'iana, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Imprisonment of Orthodox Believers (1 of 2), 1978-1983 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Imprisonment of Orthodox Believers (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Imprisonment of Orthodox Believers. Kukobaka, Mikhail, 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Imprisonment of Orthodox Believers. Soldatov, Sergei, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - State Interference in the Russian Orthodox Church Affairs. CRA Report, 1968-1974 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - State Interference in the Russian Orthodox Church Affairs. Kirov Region (1 of 2), 1960-1967 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - State Interference in the Russian Orthodox Church Affairs. Kirov Region (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - State Interference in the Russian Orthodox Church Affairs. Refusal to Register or Return Church Buildings, 1986-1989 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Closure of Churches, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Closure of Bogoiavlenskaia Church in Zhitomir, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - State Interference in the Affairs of Clergy, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Infiltration into the Russian Orthodox Church, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices toward Russian Orthodox Monasteries, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - State Interference in Theological Education, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - State Expropriation, Desecration, or Demolition of Church Buildings, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Discrimination against Orthodox Believers in Employment, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Discrimination against Orthodox Believers in Education, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry, 1974-1988 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry. Makeeva, Valeriia, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry. Starchik, Petr, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry. Zaitsev, Viacheslav, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Attacks in Media. Fr. Dmitrii Dudko (1 of 4), 1977 April (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Attacks in Media. Fr. Dmitrii Dudko (2 of 4), 1977 April (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Attacks in Media. Fr. Dmitrii Dudko (3 of 4), 1977 April (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Attacks in Media. Fr. Dmitrii Dudko (4 of 4), 1977 April (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - House Searches, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Life, 1979-1983, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Canonization and Beautification, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Services. Rituals. Liturgy, 1976, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Pilgrimages. Holy Places. Relics. Icons, 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Life of Saints, 1980, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Preaching. Conversions, 1980, 1982, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Parish Life, 1986-1991 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Publishing Department of the Moscow Patriarchate, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Brotherhood of the Patronage of the Mother of God, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Union of Orthodox Brotherhoods, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Revival. Charismatic Renewal (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Revival. Charismatic Renewal (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Monasticism, 1918, 1923, 1981-1983, 1987, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy, 1978, 1981-1983 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Denisiuk, Fr. Leontii, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (1 of 8), 1972-1974 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (2 of 8), 1975 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (3 of 8), 1976 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (4 of 8), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (5 of 8), 1978 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (6 of 8), 1979 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (7 of 8), 1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Dudko, Fr. Dmitrii (8 of 8), 1981-1987 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Feodosii, Bishop of Poltava i Kremenchug, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Feodosii, Archbishop of Astrakhan and Enotaevka, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Fonchenkov, Fr. Vasilii, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Kochetkov, Fr. Georgii, 1993, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Krasovitskii, Fr. Stefan, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Lapkovskii, Fr. Valerii, 1982-1986, 1988-1992 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Lysak, Fr. Pavel, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr, 1975-1990 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Works About (1 of 7), 1973, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 13)